taglocal.com 2011-12-31

# TagLocal.com | Privacy Policy

The protection of your privacy is extremely important to us at {SITE_SHORT_TITLE. We want you to get the information you need, but without costing your privacy. By using Tag Local, you agree to the terms and conditions listed on this privacy policy. If you cannot comply with these terms, please do not use Tag Local.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

Any information that you post on Tag Local may be shown on the site. Tag Local may log your submissions for our marketing and site improvement purposes. However, your personal information will never be used other than the user intended purpose.

We love to hear from our users! Any feedback that you leave for Tag Local will be recorded to help us improve the site. This includes your submission and the personal information you include with it. This allows us to track our feedback efficiently and quickly.

Tag Local wants the user to get everything they need from Tag Local. Because of this, we have created a login system that will feature your name and email. Once you create a login with Tag Local, you will have a more personalized viewing experience. Creating a login with Tag Local improves our customer service and creates content that is better suited for our users needs.

When you browse Tag Local, we take note of your browser type, IP address, searches, timestamp information and the pages you view. This information is used to better curate content that our users will enjoy and to personalize each visit.

We utilize the use of cookies, so that we can create a site that is personalized for each user. Cookies are used to better enhance the site experience. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your hard drive from your browser that store pieces of information. When cookies are enabled, we are automatically able to collect information. For example, you will not have to reenter your site preferences each time you visit Tag Local. You may decide to disable your use of cookies on your browser, but this will hinder your use of Tag Local.

#### PROTECTION OF INFORMATION

We take your privacy very seriously at Tag Local. We have taken strong measures to keep your personal information safe.

We will never sell, lease, rent or trade your information to outside parties. We will show advertisements from third parties that we are not affiliated with. These sites will redirect you to another website. When you are redirected from our website, we are no longer responsible for your privacy.

Tag Local may transfer non-personally identifiable information to our current our future affiliates. These affiliates may include: our parent company, joint ventures, subsidiaries, or companies under common control. These companies are required to honor our privacy policy and will never have access to your personal information.

Tag Local reserves the right to hire a third party company to acquire statistical information on our site. This information will never be personally identifiable and will include information such as how many people clicked on a certain displayed advertisement and how many daily users visit Tag Local.

Your personal information will only be shared if need to do so for legal reasons including: subpoenas, court orders, warrants or to protect the safety of our users, ourselves or the public.

#### CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

Identity theft should be taken very seriously. Tag Local wants to do our part in combating identity theft. Therefore, we have taken the steps to comply with the California Online Privacy Protect Act. Your information will never be given to a third party without your consent.

#### CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

Tag Local strongly believes that children should be safe when browsing the Internet. Because of this, we will not collect any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 and wish to use Tag Local, please consult a parent or guardian.

#### CHANGES TO THE POLICY

Tag Local reserves the right to make changes to the policy at any point. If we decide to do so, the changes will be posted on this page. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact us using our Contact Us form.

#### UNSUBSCRIBE

Your interaction with Tag Local is strictly optional. You may decide to opt out of communication by emails, notifications and mailings. If you want to unsubscribe from Tag Local, please visit our Unsubscribe page: [http://www.taglocal.com/unsubscribe/ ](http://www.taglocal.com/unsubscribe/)
